A Guide to the Katherine Gentry Bushman Papers, 1961-1997
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Katherine Gentry Bushman Papers, 1961-1997
Library of Virginia
35743
43.325 cubic feet. In part, photocopies.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of William Bushman, Staunton, Virginia, 10 March 1998.
Biographical/Historical Information
Katherine Gentry Bushman was born in Kansas City, Missouri on 1 April 1919. She married William Bushman on 30 August 1947 in Jefferson City, Missouri. They moved to Staunton, Virginia, in 1962. She was a professional genealogist, author, and local historian, as well as a charter member of the Augusta County Historical Society, one of its past presidents, and a former editor of its publication. She was also past regent of the Thomas Hughart Chapter of the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution. She died in Staunton on 9 December 1997.
Scope and Content Information
Genealogical research files of Katherine G. Bushman, including family research files, subject files, compilations, and oversize genealogical charts and maps. The majority of the collection are family research files containing correspondence with clients for whom Bushman did research, as well as genealogical notes abstracted from court records, including deed books, order books, will books, and marriage records. Patriotic organization applications, family group sheets, extracts from published sources, Bible records, census records, and genealogical charts also appear in these files. There is a substantial amount of information on the Alexander, Bell, Bushman, Craig, Curry, Davis, Fauber, Fulkerson, Greaver, Hogshead, Kinkead, McCutchan, Polk, Rankin, Robertson, Sheets, Steele, Tate, and Wilson families. Families researched are from the Shenandoah Valley region of Virginia, including Augusta, Bath, Botetourt, Rockbridge, Rockingham, and Shenandoah Counties, as well as the cities of Harrisonburg, Lexington, Staunton, and Waynesboro. There is a surname card index to these materials filed at the end of the series.
The subject files document Bushman's interests in genealogy and local history. There is information on her involvement in the Augusta County Historical Society, including her work as editor of its publication, as well her membership in the Daughters of the American Revolution. There are also transcripts of court records, correspondence, information on old homes, towns, and villages of Augusta County, tombstone inscriptions, extracts from published sources, and other historical information.
The compilations are printed sources that are both published and unpublished. They include family and local histories, as well as abstracts and indexes to court records, church records, and military records. These were compiled by Bushman and others.
Organization
Organized into four series: I. Family Research Files. II. Subject Files. III. Compilations. IV. Oversize Genealogical Charts and Maps.
Contents List
- Family Research Files (Box 1-87a)
  - "A" - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Abernathy-Logan (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adair-Shumate (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adams-Burgandine (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adams, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ailer (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alexander (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
  - Alexander (Archibald, Robert, William) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allen (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Allen, Robert (also Turk) (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - "The Allen Family Circle" (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Anderson (Box 2, Folder 2-7)
  - Anderson, Charles (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, James (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Andrew-Andrews (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Anthony (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Arbogast (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Arehart-Earhart-Airhart (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
  - Argenbright-Zimmerman (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Arion-Moyers (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong (Thomas, William, John) - Stone Ridge Farm (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - Ash-Moore-Harris-Golladay (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Aylor-Croushorn-Sheets (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "B" - Misc. (Box 3, Folder 10-13)
  - "B" - Misc. (cont.) (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Baber (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bailey (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Michael (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Balsley-Coiner (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Barclay (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bare/Bear (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bare-Ray-Christian (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Batis (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Batis-Beard (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Baumgardner, Balser (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Baylor (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Beam (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bear-Beard-Arehart-Spitler (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Beard (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Beard, Edward (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Beard-Lucas-Shuey (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Beard, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Beeton-Blakemore-Revercomb (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bell (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
  - Bell, Ann T. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bell Descendants - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bell (Long Glade) (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Bell (Stone Church) (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Bell-Erwin-Patterson (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bell-Kerr-Scanland (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary Analysis of Bell Records in Augusta County, Virginia - Compiled by Jean T. Gillett (1992) (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - A Bell Survey - Augusta County, Virginia and Some Miscellaneous Records - Compiled by Katherine G. Bushman (1987) (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
  - Belsha-Belshee (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Berry (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
  - Berry-Campbell-Givens (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Best-Vandeman-Doak-Gregg-Marsh (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Billheimer (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bing (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bird-Chestnut (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Birdwell/Burdwell (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Black (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Black-Golladay (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  - Blackburn (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Blackburn-Burnett-Marquis-Bagby-Menifee (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Blair (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Blair-Liggett-McKee (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Blakeley (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bland-Cunningham (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Blizzard (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Boggs-Lemasters (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Bolton-Trusler-Truslow (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Borden (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bosserman-Shultz (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bourland-Haynes (Mary Baldwin) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bowen (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bowman-Clemmer (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bowyer (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Bradshaw-Wamsley-Keister (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Brand (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bratton (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
  - Brawford (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Breckenridge (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Breeden (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Bridge-Brown (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bright (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Britton, Timothy (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Britton-Hamilton (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Brooks-Bashaw (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Brooks-Bashaw-Shaw (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Brown (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Francis (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Brock-Roads (Rhodes) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Brosius (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Cornelius (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Brown, James (son of John Brown and Molly Hogshead) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Brown, James Jr. & Sr. and Jonathan (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Bruce (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Brush (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Bryan-Shirley (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Buchanan (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Buchanan, Col. John (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Bumgardner (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bumgardner-Augusta County (Box 10, Folder 2-4)
  - Bumgardner, John (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Burckhardt-Burkett (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Burke-Burk (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - John Burke of Greenville (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Burke-Kivlighan (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Burke-Lamb (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Burns (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Bush (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Bushman (Box 10, Folder 13-16)
  - Bushong (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bushong-Bosang (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Buzzard-Zickafoose (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Byers (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Byrd (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "C"-Misc. (Box 11, Folder 6-11)
  - Cahoon (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Calbreath-Brydon Wilson-Hamilton (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Caldwell (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cale (Deerfield Area) - Thornton-Baldwin (Box 12, Folder 5-7)
  - Cales (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Calfee-Padgett (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Calhoon (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Calhoun, T.A. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Callahan-Marmian-Woodson (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Callaway (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Campbell (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Campbell, Hugh (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
  - Caricote (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Carlisle (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Carns/Kern/Karnes/Schaup (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Carpenter-Zimmerman (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Carroll-Helms (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Carson-Griffith-Hildebrand (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Carter (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cartmill-Anderson-Skillern (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Carver (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - Cassady (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Cathey (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Chase-Young-McComb-Palmer-Witt (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Christian (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Christian, John (also Bare) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Christian, Robert (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - Christian, William (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Christian-Henderson-Campbell-Smith (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Clark (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Clark, James (also Rhea-Elliott-Dunlap) (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
  - Clarke (Staunton) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Clatterbaugh (also Risk/Rusk) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Clemens (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Clemens-Gillham (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Clements (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Clemmer (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Clendenning (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Clinedinst (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cloninger-Merritt-Spring (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Coalter (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Coiner-Koiner (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
  - Coleman-Sheffey (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Collier (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Collins (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Collins-Griffin (Irish) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Connell (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Connelly (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Connevey-Blair-Wilson-Loop (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Connevey-Davis-Wilson (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Conrad-Fisher (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Cook-Jacob (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Cook-Lindsey-Teaford-Hanger (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Copeland (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Cosby, Dabney (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Coursey (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Cowan (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
  - Cowden-Wilson (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Cox-Wiseman-Shultz (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Crabill-Grabill (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Craig (Box 16, Folder 19-22)
  - Craig, Robert (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Craig-Duncan-McCutchan (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Crane (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Cravens (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Crawford (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Crawford (also Bell-Kerr-Laird-Christian-Paxton) (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
  - Crickenbarger (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Crist (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Crobarger-Shields (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Crockett (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Croft-Haines-Miller-Bailey-Brower (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Cromwell-Roop (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Crone (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Crosby (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
  - Croson (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Cross-Hunter (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Crow-Lewis-Donnelly-Gillsepy (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Culp (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cunningham (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cupp-Fall (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Cupp-Fall-Swoop (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Curry (Box 18, Folder 8-13)
  - Cushing (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "D" - Misc. (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - Dabney (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Daggy (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Daggy-Mallow (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Dannemora (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Dalhouse (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Darcus (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Darst-Torbett (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Daugherty-McClelland (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Davis (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Davis-Davies (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Davis-Cunningham-Reeves-Landes-Rogers (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
  - Davis (Davis Fancy) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Davis, Braxton (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Davis, C. Braxton (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Davisson (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Deffenbaugh-Hogshead-Hupman (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Dehart (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Dellinger-Bunch-Baskin (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - DePriest (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - DePriest - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - DePriest - Early Records (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - DePriest, Robert Hundley Sr. (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
  - Deverix (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Dickson-Dixon (also Tedford-Telford) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Diddle (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Deitrich-Anderson (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Dobbins-Holeman-Stephenson (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Doak-Breckenridge (Box 21, Folder 5-7)
  - Dobbs-Evy (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Donaghe-White-Baldwin (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Donahoo-Garvin-Young-McComb (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Donaldson-Dold (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Douglass-Thompson (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Downey (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Drawdy (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Drumgold (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Drummond (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Dull (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
  - Duncan (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
  - Dunston (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "E" - Misc. (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
  - Eakle-Eagle (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Eckert (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Edmiston (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
  - Elliott (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Elliott-Steele-Shultz-Smith-Hawpe-Mizer-Swink-Wilson- Bumgardner-McGilvray (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Emmett (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Engleman (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Engleman-Silling (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Erwin (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
  - Eskridge-Wall-Covell (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Estill-Campbell (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
  - Eutzler (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Evans (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
  - Eversole (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Evick (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Ewell-Kennerley (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Ewing-Hahn (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - "F" - Misc. (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
  - Faber Family Reunion-June 27 & 27, 1993-Spottswood, Va. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Fackler (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Fackler-Smith-Peer-Paul (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fairburn (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Farrier-Caldwell-Kinkead (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Fauber, Christian (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Fauber, Jacob (Box 24, Folder 11-14)
  - Fauber, John (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fauber, Peter (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Fauber, Valentine Jr. (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Fauber-Valentine Jr. (Old Records) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fauber-Brownfield (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Fauber-Summers-Cress (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fauber-Misc. (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
  - Fifer (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Finley (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - Fisher (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Fisher, Adam (Rockingham) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, John (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Fisher-Grove-Kennedy-Brown (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Fisher-Lankford (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Fisher-Shaddon-Steele (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Fitzpatrick (Box 26, Folder 10-11)
  - Fitzwater (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Fix-Fulwider (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  - Flack-Harman-Clarke-McCune (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Fletcher-Hindman (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Floyd (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Forsythe-Hook (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fowler-Whitley-Fullen-Magill (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fox-Kindig-Padgett-McClurer-Silling-Rankin-Wine (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Frame (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Frank (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fraser, Samuel (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Frazier (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
  - Fridley (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
  - Frogge (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Frymyer/Frymoyer (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Fugate-Mahon (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Fulkerson, Abraham (Folder 28, Folder 1)
  - Derrick Fulkerson (Father of Brothers) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Fulkerson, Frederick (Box 28, Folder 3-5)
  - Fulkerson, Fulker (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Fulkerson, James (Box 28, Folder 7-9)
  - Fulkerson, John (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Fulkerson, John (of Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Fulkerson, Peter and Richard (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Fulkerson (Mrs. Zerkle) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Fulkerson-New Jersey-Wills (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Fulkersons in Northern Virginia (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Fulkerson - Correspondence - Aronhime (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Fulkerson Descendants Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Fulkerson Correspondence - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Fulton (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Fultz-Hanger (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Fulwider (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Fulwider-Arehart (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Fulwider-Lowman (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Funkhouser (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "G"-Misc. (Box 29, Folder 8-11)
  - Gabbert (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
  - Garber (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
  - Garber, Rev. Samuel (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Garber-Merritt (Box 30, Folder 5-8)
  - Gardiner-Evans-Brumley-Wright (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Garrison-Barger (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Gatlive (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Gay (Box 30, Folder 12-13)
  - Gearing (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Gentry (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
  - George (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Gibbs (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Gibson (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Gilbert-McDaniel-Stanton (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Gilkeson-Coursey (Box 31, Folder 12-13)
  - Gillespie-Huston (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Gillham-Campbell-Clements (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Givens-Lam (Lamme) (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Glasgow (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Glendy-Guy (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Gochenour (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Goen-Weitzel (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Goldman (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Golladay (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
  - Good (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Goodpastor (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
  - Goode (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Gorden-Rush (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Goul (Gaul)-Bratton-Lockridge (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Graham (Box 32, Folder 14-15)
  - Grainger (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Gray-Gullett (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Gray-Hathaway (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Greaver (Box 33, Folder 1-6)
  - Greaver-Bright-Thomas-Shott (Box 33, Folder 7-11)
  - Greene (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Greenlee (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Gregg (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Gregory (Box 34, Folder 3-5)
  - Gregory-Gladwell (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
  - Greiner (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Greiner-Valentine-Yost (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Grider/Greider (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
  - Griffith (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Grim (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Groah-Zink-Summers (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Grove, Christian (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Grove-Bright-Rankin-Seawright (Box 35, Folder 4-6)
  - Grove (Martin & Benj.)-Landes-Harshbarger-Wenger-Beery- Hildebrand (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
  - Grove-Clyde-Van Dyke (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Grove-Stover-Lamb-Staubus (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Gum (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
  - Guthrie-Hall-Frazer-White (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Gwin/Gwinn (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - "H" - Misc. (Box 36, Folder 1-7)
  - Haddan/Haddon (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Haffner (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Haffner-Swisher (Box 36, Folder 10-12)
  - Hahn (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Hair/Hare (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Hair-Stephenson-Wooddell (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
  - Hall (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Hall, Carmaine (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
  - Hall-Callison-Mitchell (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Hall-Webb-Ailshire (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Ham (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Hamacher (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Hamilton (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Hanger (Box 37, Folder 13-15)
  - Hanger, Peter Sr. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Hanger-Liptrap (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Hanna, Robert (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Hannah/Hanna (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Hardbarger (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Hardy-Bowles-Brittain (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Harman (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Harman-Catlett-Garber (Box 38, Folder 8-10)
  - Harnsberger (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Harper (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Harris (Box 38, Folder 13-15)
  - Harris-Harrison (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Harry (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Haton-Sterns (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Hawkins (Borden) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Hawpe-Dunlap-Mizer (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
  - Hayden (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Hayes (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
  - Hays-Lush-Vance-Miles (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Hays-Moffett (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Hayslett-Moore (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Heizer (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
  - Hemp (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Henderson (Box 40, Folder 1-8)
  - Henderson-Crawford (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Henry-Sharp-Patterson (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
  - Hemp-Ellinger-Olinger-Grant (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Hendren (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Heppert, E.D. Jr. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Hess-Sensabaugh (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Hewitt-Cease-Sibert (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Hight-Taylor (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Hildebrand (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Hinds-Kerr-Francis (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Hiner (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Hippard-Spears (Box 41, Folder 8-9)
  - Hite (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Michael Hite-Jemima Jones (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Hodam (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Hodge-Fawcett (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Hogg (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Hogshead-Gilkeson (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - Hogsett/Hogshead (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Holbrook (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Holmes (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Holston (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Hoof-Fellers-Bailey-Root-Parr (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Hotchkiss, Jed (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Houchin (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Houston-Curry (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Houston-Huston-Montgomery (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Howdyshell (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Huff-Kaufmann-Gayheart (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
  - Huffman-Showalter (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Hughart (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Hull (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Hull-Beard-Baylor (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Hull-Cale-Summers-Hunter-Hanger-Rusmisel (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Hull-Summers-Beck-Henderson (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Hulvey-White-Sheets-Cupp (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Humphries (Box 43, Folder 11-12)
  - Hunter (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Hunter-Cross-Ewing-Diddle-Stephenson (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - Hunter-Seawright-Watts-Young-Wise-Sites (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Hutchens-Parris-Beard-Spindle-Hudson (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Hutton-Cunningham (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "I" - Misc. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Imboden-Graham-Gibson (Box 44, Folder 7-9)
  - Ingram (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - "J" - Misc. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Jackson (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Jackson-Fridley (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - James (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Jennings (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Jesse (Box 45, Folder 1-6)
  - Joh (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Johns (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Johnson-Dawson-Gordon (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Johnson-Johnston (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Johnston (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Johnston-Carter (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Johnston-Faris-Henkle (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Johnston, Zachariah (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - Jones-Griffith-Russell (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Jordan-Masincup (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Joyce-Sherman (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - "K" - Misc. (Box 46, Folder 7-9)
  - Keiser, Samuel (also Null) (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Keller-Landes (Box 46, Folder 11-12)
  - Kelly (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
  - Kenney (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Kent-Wheelbarger (also Abraham Sheets) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Kerr (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Kidd (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Kile (Goil-Goyle) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Kimberlin (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Kinder-Gintner (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - King (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Kinkead, David (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Kinkead, John Esq. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Kinkead, Thomas (m. Isabelle Kinkead) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Kinkead, William (Stiller) (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Kinkead-Misc. Records (Box 47, Folder 13-14)
  - Kinkead-Gay (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Kinnear (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Kirkham (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Kirkham, Jacob (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Kirkpatrick-Finley-Reid (Reed) (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Kite-Windlekite (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Knighton (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Knowles (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Koontz-Kunz-Coons (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Kunkle (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Kyle, Jacob (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - "L" - Misc. (Box 48, Folder 7-11)
  - La Porte (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
  - Lamb-Dickey-Wise-Young-Sherman (Box 49, Folder 1-4)
  - Lamb-Huff-Kiblinger (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Lambert (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Landes (Box 49, Folder 7-9)
  - Lane (Lain)-Shown (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Lange (also Washburn) (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Lavell (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
  - Layman - Maryland and Virginia (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Leake (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Ledderdale (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Ledgerwood (Box 50, Folder 7-9)
  - Leeper (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Leitch-Ligon (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Lemon (Box 50, Folder 12-13)
  - Leonard (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Lessley (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Lewis (Box 51, Folder 1-3)
  - Lewis, George (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Lilly-Doak (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Lingle/Lingell (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Linn-Kyger-Harshman (Box 51, Folder 7)